http://www.whatkatiedid.com/pages/security-and-cookie-policy

Hey Doll, All of our lingerie comes in sizes 10-18 so you only need to search if your are outside this size range. All of our corsets come in reduced waist sizes 18" to 34".
Dress/Corset Size
UK 8
UK 10
UK 12
UK 14
UK 16
UK 18
UK 20
40F
Hey Doll, All of our lingerie comes in sizes 10-18 so you only need to search if your are outside this size range. All of our corsets come in reduced waist sizes 18" to 34".
Dress/Corset Size
UK 8
UK 10
UK 12
UK 14
UK 16
UK 18
UK 20
Shop by Collection
Yva Lingerie (Seasonal Black and Red)
Maitresse Lingerie (Black)
Harlow Lingerie (Peach)
Glamour Shapewear (Black and Peach)
1940s Map Lingerie (Multi)
CC09 Lingerie (Black and Peach)
Liz Lingerie (Black)
Loungewear (Black and Peach)
Retro Lingerie (Black and Peach)
Jean Lingerie (Seasonal Peach)
Shop Clothing
Fashion by What Katie Did
Splendette Jewellery
Bow and Crossbones Jewellery
Long Gloves
Shop Stockings
Seamed Stockings: Neutrals
Seamed Stockings: Colours
Shop by Collection
Yva Lingerie (Seasonal Black and Red)
Maitresse Lingerie (Black)
Harlow Lingerie (Peach)
Glamour Shapewear (Black and Peach)
1940s Map Lingerie (Multi)
CC09 Lingerie (Black and Peach)
Liz Lingerie (Black)
Loungewear (Black and Peach)
Retro Lingerie (Black and Peach)
Jean Lingerie (Seasonal Peach)
Shop Clothing
Fashion by What Katie Did
Splendette Jewellery
Bow and Crossbones Jewellery
Long Gloves
Shopping FAQs
Shipping Times
Returns
Our Website
Our website platform is hosted by Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.
Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.
When placing an order you have the choice of paying by Shopify Payments which is fully PCI compliant. You can find out more information about their payment system by clicking here.
You also have the option of paying by Paypal (website payment standard)
or Amazon Payments.
Email Marketing
You will receive email newsletters from us if you have signed up to our mailing list either online, in our London boutique, or at one of our pop up boutiques.
An unsubscribe button can be found at the bottom of every marketing email you receive.
Our marketing emails are sent via Mailchimp. You can read their security policy by clicking here.
Online Marketing
Our current online advertising platforms are Google, Facebook (which also includes Instagram) and AdRoll. If you accept cookies or follow us on Facebook then you might see our adverts pop up on Facebook, Instagram or the AdRoll Display Network.
To change your Google Advert Settings click here.
To change your Facebook and Instagram Advert Settings click here.
To opt out of AdRoll remarketing ads click here.
Direct Mail Marketing
We send our printed magazine to valued customers in the UK up to three times per year alongside occasional invites to special events. To opt out of direct mail please send your full name and address to media@whatkatiedid.com
Cookies
When you visit our site, a cookie may be saved on your computer (if your computer accepts cookies), and if you return to the site the cookie may be read. We use cookies to help us collect the site visitation data.
A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.
Some parts of our website use cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. We do not correlate this information with data about individual users, nor do we share this information or sell it to any third party.
If you prefer not to receive cookies on our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to view any area of our website, but you will need to have cookies turned on to place an order online. If you would prefer to order by telephone you can call us on 0345 430 8743.
To find our how to turn off cookies click here.
Third Party Websites
Our website, in particular our online magazine, contains links to other third party websites. This privacy notice does not cover these links or the way that your personal data may be used by the third parties who operate these sites. Please read carefully any privacy policies on other websites you visit, particularly before providing any personal information.
Your Privacy
Your privacy is very important to us. We will never sell or give your details to any other company.
Your Information
You can request details of and a copy of the personal information that we hold about you by making a subject access request under the Data Protection Act 1998. Please contact the Data Protection Officer at the address below to make a request. A small charge may apply.
We want to make sure that all of the information we hold about you is accurate and up to date so please let us know if we have got anything wrong.
If you have any questions, concerns or comments about this privacy notice or our use of your personal information please contact us:
Data Protection Officer
What Katie Did, Unit 8 The Old Mill, 61 Reading Road, Pangbourne, Berkshire, RG8 7HY
YOU'RE INVITED TO JOIN CLUB WHAT KATIE DID Join our club to receive our best discounts, new videos, previews and styling tips every week by email. Enter your email to join Club What Katie Did now!
